Guide to the Associated Students of Stanford University Records SC0009
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- General Records, Series 5
  - Hours for Recreational Buildings, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Speaker's Bureau, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Stanford Alumni Association, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Stanford Historical Society, 1981-1983 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Stanford Tour Information, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Student Insurance, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Theater Guild, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Social Security and Student Identification Numbers, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Stanford Bookstore, 1971, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Strike, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Student/Faculty Relations Dept. of Economics Related to Foley Case, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Sunday Flicks, 1977-1981 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - SWOPSI 141 wk. 5, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - SWOPSI 141--Research Reporter, 1982/1977? (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - SWOPSI 141--"The New Student Power and Needed Educational Reforms", 1977 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - SWOPSI 141--"Lyman traces historical development of student role in governance", 1976-1982 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - SWOPSI 141--"Four Models of a University", 1982 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - SWOPSI 141-- "Student Participation in University Decision Making", 1982 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - SWOPSI 141-- "Student Power and the University Experience", 1982 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - SWOPSI 141-- "Organizing Students on Campus", 1978, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - SWOPSI 141-- "The Evolution of Planning Models at Stanford University", 1979, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - SWOPSI 141-- "The Dynamics of Student Rebellion", 1979, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - SWOPSI 141-- "Continuity and Change: The New Left in the Context of American Student Activism", 1979, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - SWOPSI 141-- "Student Activism in the 1970s and 1980s", 1979, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Study on Education at Stanford--Proposal for Change to Semester System, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Gaieties, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - ASSU: Orientation Night, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Rushbook, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Draft copy of ASSU guide (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Student organization sourcebook, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - COP priorities, 1979-80 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Scheduling events (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Reports, miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Cardinal's Board announcements (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Student-Faculty boards (includes copy of The Stanford Professor), 1961-1967 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Pre-Registration Commission / Committee, 1957-1965 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Foreign Scholarship Commission brochure, circa 1955 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - ASSU Centennial Commission Newsletter, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Concert series (includes brochure on Paul Robeson concerrt), 1931-1967 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Committee on Student Services and Affairs, 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Council on Religious Affairs lecture announcements (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - ASSU Sunday Flicks flyers, 1973-1979 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - ASSU Scholarships notices, 1961-1963 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Summer Manager's Intern Program press release, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Library Commission brochure (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Travel Services, 1971-1977 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Political Union Focus (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Guide to ASSU Activities, 1952-1961 and undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Enology Club class list, undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Bar Tending Class clipping, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Institute of International Relations, 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - News Clippings, 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Scrapbook of clippings relating to women's groups and issues, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook of clippings relating to student activities, 1978-1982 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Athletic awards, 1927 Oct-1932 Jun (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Athletic Awards, 1932 Nov-1935 May (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Athletic Awards, 1935 Nov-1938 Jun (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Athletic Awards, 1938 Nov-1943 Jun (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Athletic Awards, 1946 Mar-1953 Jun (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Athletic awards, 1953 Nov-1958 Feb (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - ASSU Foreign Scholars' Reports, 1948-1962 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Bound volume contains narrative reports by the individual scholars, correspondence, and a few miscellaneous items.
- Organizations, Series 6
  This series largely consists of bound reports from the Dramatic Council and the Publications Council. The Dramatic Council reports, 1925-1941, include expenses, budgets, contracts, some correspondence, minutes, and narrative reports. The Publications Council reports, 1931-1932 and 1938-1967, include financial information on the Chaparral, Quad, and Daily, and Publications Council minutes. Records for the 1932/33 through 1938/39 academic years are included in Student Manager's reports in Series 3. Other records in this series include bound volumes containing constitutions and by-laws of student organizations, 1920-1963, and miscellaneous files from the Publications Council.
  - Dramatic Council Reports, 1925-1926 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Dramatic Council Reports, 1926-1927 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Dramatic Council Reports, 1927-1928 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Dramatic Council Reports, 1928-1929 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Dramatic Council Reports, 1929-1930 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dramatic Council Reports, 1930-1931 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Dramatic Council Reports, 1931-1932 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Dramatic Council Reports, 1932-1934 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Dramatic Council Reports, 1934-1935 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Dramatic Council Reports, 1935-1936 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Dramatic Council Reports, 1935-1936 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Dramatic Council Reports, 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Dramatic Council Reports, 1939-1941 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Publications' Reports, 1931-1932 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Publications' Reports, 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Publications' Reports, 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Publications' Reports, 1940-1941 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Publications' Reports, 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Publications' Reports, 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Publications' Reports, 1943-1944 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Publications' Reports, 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Publications' Reports, 1945-1946 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Publications' Reports, 1946-1947 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Publications' Reports, 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Publications' Reports, 1948-1949 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Publications' Reports, 1949-1950 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Publications' Reports, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Publications' Reports, 1951-1952 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Publications' Reports, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Publications' Reports, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Publications' Reports, 1954-1955 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Publications' Reports, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Publications' Reports, 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Publications' Reports, 1957-1958 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Publications' Reports, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Publications' Reports, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Publications' Reports, 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Publications' Reports, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Publications' Reports, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Publications' Reports, 1963-1964 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Publications' Reports, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Publications' Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Handbook for Student Organizations, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Publications Workshop, 1966-1969 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Student Organization Registration Cards, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Student Organization Registration Cards, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Student Organization Registration Cards, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Student Organization Registration Cards, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Student Organization Registration Cards, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Publications Board, 1967-1972 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Publications Board, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Publications Board, 1975-1979 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Publications Board, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Constitutions and by-laws of various organizations Volume 1, 1920-1959 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Constitutions Volume II, 1946-1956 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Constitutions Volume III, 1949-1956 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Constitutions Volume IV, 1952-1961 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Constitutions Volume V, 1954-1960 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Constitutions Volume VI, 1957-1963 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Course Guides, Series 7
  The Course Guide series contains the published Course Guides and Course Reviews, computer printouts on the tabulation of questionnaire data, and general administrative files.
  - Distribution Aid, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Distribution (Plans), 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Lance Friedman's Letter and Responses, 1972-1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Request for Inclusion in Course Guide, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Operation Plan, Financial Stats-Temporary, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Feasibility Study, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - ASSU Course Guide Job Applications, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - ASSU Course Guide-Mailer, Autumn Quarter, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - ASSU Course Guide-Mailer, Spring Quarter, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - ASSU Course Guide-Mailer Responses, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ASSU Course Guide-Overseas Studies, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ASSU Course Guide Personnel, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - ASSU Course Guide; Questionnaire Circulation, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - ASSU Course Guide; Questionnaire Design, 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - ASSU Course Guide; Questionnaires, 1971-1976 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Report on the Evaluation and Improvement of Teaching, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - ASSU Course Guide: Reviews, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - ASSU Course Guide: Survey Coordination Schedules, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - ASSU Course Guide: Supplement, Spring, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - ASSU Course Guide: Statistics, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - ASSU Course Guide: ASSU Senate, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - ASSU Course Guide: Advertising Contracts, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - ASSU Course Guide: Invoices, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - ASSU Course Guide: Advertising Contracts, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - ASSU Course Guide: Advertising Contracts, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - ASSU Course Guide: Advertising Contracts, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - ASSU Course Guide: Advertising Contracts, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - ASSU Course Guide: Invoices, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - ASSU Course Guide: Financial Material, Course Ratings, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - ASSU Course Guide: Info for Business Manager, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - ASSU Course Guide: Chron. File (Correspondence, Invoices, etc.), 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - ASSU Course Guide: Correspondence; April-August 1980 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Committee on the Evaluation and Improvement of Teaching (CEIT); Adhoc Subcommittee on Student Needs, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Committee on the Evaluation and Improvement of Teaching: Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - ASSU Course Guide: Computer Accounts, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - ASSU Course Guide: Course Offerings (Departmental), 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - ASSU Course Guide: Computer Notes, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Subcommittee on the Evaluation and Improvement of Teaching, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Committee for the Evaluation and Improvement of Teaching: Ad hoc (Evaluation); part 1, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Committee for the Evaluation and Improvement of Teaching: Ad hoc (Evaluation); part 2, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Committee for the Evaluation and Improvement of Teaching: Ad hoc (Improvement), 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - ASSU Course Guide: Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - ASSU Course Guide: Distribution Materials, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Course Guide, 1976 Autumn (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Course Guide, 1977 Autumn (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Course Guide, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Course Guide, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Course Guide, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - ASSU Task Force on Tenure and Teaching, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - ASSU Course Reviews- The Guerrilla, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - ASSU Course Review, 1965-1978 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Course GuideAutumn, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Course Guide Winter, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Course Guide Spring, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Course Guide Spring, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Course Guide Fall, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Course Guide Winter, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Course Guide Spring, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Course Guide Fall, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Course Guide Winter, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Course Guide Fall, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Course Guide Winter, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Course Guide Spring, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Course Guide Fall, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Course Guide Winter, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Course Guide Spring, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Course Guide Fall, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Course Guide Winter, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Course Guide Spring, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Course Review, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Course Review, 1972/1973 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Course Review, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Scratch Sheet, circa 1957 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Course Guide Tabulation of Questionnaire Data Autumn Quarter, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Course Guide Tabulation of Questionnaire Data Autumn Quarter, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Course Guide Tabulation of Questionnaire Data Winter Quarter, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Course Guide Tabulation of Questionnaire Data Autumn Quarter, 1975/1976 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Course Guide Tabulation of Questionnaire Data Winter Quarter, 1975/1976 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Course Guide Tabulation of Questionnaire Data Spring Quarter, 1975/1976 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Course Guide Tabulation of Questionnaire Data Autumn Quarter, 1976/1977 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Course Guide Tabulation of Questionnaire Data Winter Quarter, 1976/1977 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Course Guide Tabulation of Questionnaire Extra Data Winter Quarter, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Course Guide Tabulation of Questionnaire Extra Data Spring Quarter, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Course Guide Statistics, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Course Guide Tabulation of Questionnaire Data Spring Quarter, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Course Guide Tabulation of Questionnaire Data Autumn Quarter, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Course Guide Tabulation of Questionnaire Data Overseas Studies Winter, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Course Guide Statistics Overseas Studies Winter, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Course Guide Statistics, miscellaneous programs and printouts, 1974 and undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - ASSU Course Guide (computer tape), circa 1977 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-1984-024
  - ASSU constitution and by-laws, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - ASSU constitution, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - ASSU constitution updated June 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - ASSU letters of acceptance 1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Constitutional correspondence 1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Constitution revision, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Amendments 1965-69 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Amendments 1970-75 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Constitution revision, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - ASSU constitution general information, 1973-81 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - ASSU correspondence to 1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence form ASSU 1982 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence re ASSU 1981-82 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - ASSU general correspondence, 1983-84 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - ASSU general correspondence, 1980-81 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - ASSU correspondence, 1963-73 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - ASSU Miscellaneous 1981-82 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - ASSU general 1976-81 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - ASSU RSVP list 1984 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - ASSU council of Presidents 1967-79 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - COP 1979-80 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - COP 1982-83 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - ASSU COP 1970-84 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - ASSU COP meetings, information, 1981-82 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - COP 1980-81 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - ECC 1976 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - ASSU elections and fee assessments 1979-82 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - ASSU fee assessments 1976-82 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - General ASSU financial information, 1976-82 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Friends and Helpers – ASSU Special Project, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - ASSU VSO banking policies, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - ASSU: budget information 1981-82 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - ASSU: Minority Affairs Task Force 1982 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - ASSU: Advisement Concerns, 1981-82 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - ASSU: Daily articles (and others) 1982-84 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - ASSU guest professorships, 1968-78 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Honor Code 1967-79 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Statement on Faculty Self-Discipline 1971-72 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - SJC 1978-79 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Stanford Judicial Council Candidates, 1982-83 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Judicial System 1973-76 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Judicial System 1971-72 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Judicial System 1969-70 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Judicial System 1965-68 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - SCLC 1971-75 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - ASSU Nominations Committee 1977-82 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - ASSU Nominations Committee 1973-76 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - ASSU Nominations Committee 1969-72 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Nominations Committee 1979 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - ASSU Nominations Committee Information 1982 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - ASSU Lobby Office 1984 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - ASSU Publications 1983 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Publications Board 1978-80 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Publications Workshop 1967-69 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - ASSU Relationship with University (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Constitution, By-laws 1977-79 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - ASSU Reorganization 1974-83 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - ASSU Constitution and Organization 1975-76 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - ASSU Senate 1983-84 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Senate Orientation Manual 1971-79 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Senate Orientation 1978-80 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - ASSU Senate Orientation 1981-82 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Lecture Notes 1974 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Speakers Bureau 1979 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - ASSU Speakers Bureau 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - ASSU Newsletters (correspondent) 1982 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - ASSU Newsletters 1980-82 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - ASSU elections 1981-82 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - ASSU elections report 1982-84 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Elections 1980-82 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - ASSU Treasurer's Handbook 1973-82 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - ASSU Senate 1980-81 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Senate Agenda Packets 1980-81 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Senate Orientation 1980-81 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - ASSU Executive Council Meetings, information, etc. 1981-82 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - ASSU Financial Manager Meeting minutes, information 1981-82 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - ASSU Financial Manager 1980-81 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Meeting minutes – Senate Chair 1981 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Senate Committee Meeting information 1980-84 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Senate Minutes 1977-78 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Senate Minutes 1977-78 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Senate Minutes 1978-79 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - ASSU Minutes/1979-80 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - ASSU Senate Meeting, Agenda, etc. 1981-82 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - ASSU Documents 1983 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - ASSU binder (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Senate Meeting Notes, Feb. 22-Apr. 5, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Senate Meeting Notes, Apr. 19-May 3, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Senate Meeting Notes, May 17-18, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Senate Meeting Notes, May 24, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Senate Meeting Notes, June 26-Aug. 2, 1983, summer session (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Senate Meeting Notes, Nov. 1, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Senate Meeting Notes, Nov. 8, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Senate Meeting Notes, Nov. 29, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Senate Meeting Notes, Sept. 27, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Senate Meeting Notes, Jan. 17-31, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - ASSU Senate Meeting, Mar. 6, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - ASSU Senate Meeting, March/April 1983-84 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - ASSU Senate Apr. 24, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - ASSU Senate Meeting May 10, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - ASSU Minutes, Feb. 14, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - ASSU Senate Meetings 1983-84 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - ASSU Senate May 22, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - 15th Senate Meeting June 16, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - ASSU Senate 1983, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - C-15 Proposal, 1974-75 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2006-238
  Records in accession 2006-238 include constitution and by-laws, elections materials, senate records, reports, committee records, and general program and administrative materials.
  - Nominations Commission - University Committee Applications #1, May, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Nominations Commission - University Committee Applications #2, May, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Nominations Commission - University Committee Applications #3, May, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Nominations Commission - University Committee Applications #4, May, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Nominations Commission - University Committee Applications #5, May, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Nominations Commission - Spring Cycle, 2004 (Box 1)
  - Nominations Commission - Fall Cycle, 2004 (Box 1)
  - Nominations Commission - University Committee Applications, 2004 (Box 1)
  - University Committee Materials Miscellaneous (2 folders) (Box 1)
  - Working Constitution and By-Laws, 1999-2000 (Box 2)
  - Working Constitution and By-Laws, 1999-2000 (Box 2)
  - ASSU Constitution and Joint By-Laws, May, 2002 (Box 2)
  - ASSU Constitution and Joint By-Laws, May, 2002 (Box 2)
  - "Official Constitution, By-Laws, Rules of Order, and Standing Rules", 1998 (Box 2)
  - Comparison of 1998 and 1999 ASSU Constitutions (Box 2)
  - ASSU Constitution, 1998 (Box 2)
  - "Associated Students of the University of Washington - Articles of Incorporation, Constitution, Bylaws, Student Senate Handbook, Election Policies, Personnel Policies, 1997-98 Budget", September, 1997 (Box 2)
  - ASSU By-Laws, 1995 (Box 2)
  - ASSU Constitution, 1995 (Box 2)
  - Associated Students of the University of Washington Guide, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
  - Graduate Student Council Bulletins, 2000-2002 (Box 2)
  - Nominations of Student Representatives History and Background Material, July, 2001 (Box 2)
  - ASSU Executive Materials, 2004-2005 (Box 2)
  - ASSU Annual Report, 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1960-1961 (Box 2)
  - "ASSU Book Service, Bazaar Proposal", 2003 (Box 3)
  - News Readership Program, 2002 (Box 3)
  - Absolute Fun Full Moon, 2003-2004 (Box 3)
  - Tresidder Advisory Board, Spring 2003 (Box 3)
  - Campaign for Student Space #1, March, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Campaign for Student Space #2, March, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Student Activity Space Master Plan, December, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Tresidder Union Taskforce Report, June, 1994 (Box 3)
  - Undergraduate Student Life Report, July, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Graduate Qualify of Life at Stanford - Analysis and Recommendation, January, 2002 (Box 3)
  - Graduate Qualify of Life at Stanford - Analysis and Recommendation, January, 2002 (Box 3)
  - "The Report of the Dean of Students' Working Group on Lesbian, Gay, and Bisexual Student Needs" (Box 3)
  - Report of the Graduate Health Care Task Force, May, 2004 (Box 3)
  - The Murals of Terra, 1997-1998 (Box 3)
  - ASSU Elections, 2000 (Box 4)
  - Student Organization Handbook, 2001-2002 (Box 4)
  - ASSU Elections Handbook, Spring, 1997 (Box 4)
  - ASSU Elections Materials, 2001-2002 (Box 4)
  - ASSU Elections Materials, 2002-2003 (Box 4)
  - ASSU Elections Materials, 1999 (Box 4)
  - ASSU Elections Materials, 1996 (Box 4)
  - ASSU Elections Materials, 1998 (Box 4)